<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>HACKED Blog</title>
  <subtitle>Learn&amp;gt;Build&amp;gt;Share</subtitle>
  <id>http://hacked.io/blog/</id>
  <link href="http://hacked.io/blog/"/>
  <link href="http://hacked.io/blog/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2013-06-18T17:04:00Z</updated>
  <author>
    <name>The HACKED Team</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Volunteer at HACKED</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="/blog/2013/06/18/volunteer-at-hacked/"/>
    <id>/blog/2013/06/18/volunteer-at-hacked/</id>
    <published>2013-06-18T17:04:00Z</published>
    <updated>2013-06-18T17:04:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>The HACKED Team</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Think you can help make HACKED happen? Well we have now opened up volunteer signup so head on over to &lt;a href='http://hacked.io/volunteer'&gt;http://hacked.io/volunteer&lt;/a&gt; to find out more!&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>It's a SELL OUT!</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="/blog/2013/06/11/its-a-sell-out/"/>
    <id>/blog/2013/06/11/its-a-sell-out/</id>
    <published>2013-06-11T15:45:00Z</published>
    <updated>2013-06-11T15:45:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>The HACKED Team</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In an amazing time of six minutes you all snapped up the final two hundred tickets! Now if you did not get a ticket there&amp;#8217;s still a chance you can come to HACKED. We have now launched the waiting list which is available on the &lt;a href='/waitinglist'&gt;waiting list&lt;/a&gt; page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How will it work?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From early July we will start asking people who can&amp;#8217;t make HACKED to return their tickets. From this pool we randomly allocate these tickets to those on the waiting list. If you are lucky enough to receive one of these tickets you will have a 24 hour window in which to complete your sign-up. If you miss the 24 hour window the ticket will be reallocated to someone else on the list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hope to see many of you at HACKED next month!&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>The Final 200 tickets</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="/blog/2013/05/29/the-final-200-tickets/"/>
    <id>/blog/2013/05/29/the-final-200-tickets/</id>
    <published>2013-05-29T08:30:00Z</published>
    <updated>2013-05-29T08:30:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>The HACKED Team</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Over the past two weeks we have had many long meetings, several heated games of rock-paper-scissors-lizard-Spock and moved around lots of chairs to try to squeeze as many of you as possible into our HACKED venue!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The outcome is we have decided to release the final batch of tickets on Wednesday 12th June at 1pm. As this is the final release of tickets we will be opening the waiting list immediately after the tickets have sold out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The exact process for the waiting list will be announced in early July. We hope it will allow an extra 50-100 people to attend HACKED as tickets are returned from cancellations, unused sponsor allocations, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So set a reminder in your calendar, and we hope to see many of you at HACKED.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Ticketing Update</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="/blog/2013/05/08/ticketing-update/"/>
    <id>/blog/2013/05/08/ticketing-update/</id>
    <published>2013-05-08T06:56:00Z</published>
    <updated>2013-05-08T06:56:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>The HACKED Team</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;You&amp;#8217;re an enthusiastic lot, aren&amp;#8217;t you? Ten days ago we released the initial batch of 200 HACKED tickets. We did our best to promote the event and the ticket release, but even then we couldn&amp;#8217;t predict how keen you all were; all 200 tickets were snapped up within 4 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;4 freakin&amp;#8217; minutes. WOW!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since then we&amp;#8217;ve gotten a lot of replies, real life requests and hints of bribes* from those of you that haven&amp;#8217;t managed to get a ticket yet. Don&amp;#8217;t despair, we will be releasing more tickets in the upcoming weeks. In fact, the next (smaller) batch of tickets will be live next week at 8:00am (yep, that&amp;#8217;s 8 in the morning) on Tuesday the 14th of May.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why release tickets this way? Why not release them all in one go? Well, there are multiple reasons&amp;#8230;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For starters, we&amp;#8217;ve got over a thousand people signed up to our mailing list and we want to give everyone a fair chance in getting a ticket.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Releasing the tickets at different times and days will give everyone interested a chance of getting a ticket.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Some of the tickets still need to be allocated to people involved in running the event, like volunteers, sponsors, press and speakers.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Finally, we admit, it also doesn&amp;#8217;t hurt to be talked about. The more interest we can generate in the event, without spending money on marketing, the more value we offer our great sponsors. It&amp;#8217;s only with their help can we produce the best event possible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So get your itchy trigger fingers ready for Tuesday the 14th! By the way, if you&amp;#8217;re interested in the other events we run, there are still tickets available for &lt;a href='http://barcampberkshire.com/'&gt;BarCamp Berkshire 2&lt;/a&gt; on the 15th/16th June.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*The HACKED Team will in no circumstances accept bribes. Unless ponies are involved. Or zeppelins.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>The waiting is over</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="/blog/2013/04/24/the-waiting-is-over/"/>
    <id>/blog/2013/04/24/the-waiting-is-over/</id>
    <published>2013-04-24T19:49:00Z</published>
    <updated>2013-04-24T19:49:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>The HACKED Team</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Two years ago we wondered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What if?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What if we could organize an epic hackday, the likes of which London hasn&amp;#8217;t seen for a while? What if we could find an amazing venue that could host us? What if we brought 500 awesome developers and designers together and let their creativity loose on the world? What if we were crazy enough to try and pull this off?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has taken us two years since we first started plotting and planning this: today we are thrilled to confirm that HACKED will be taking place at The O2 on July 20th and 21st.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will provide you and 499 other developers, designers, hardware hackers and tinkerers with inspiring talks, tasty food and a fantastic venue. All you need to do is bring your ideas and a sleeping bag and you&amp;#8217;ll have a chance to make new friends and build awesome stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first round of tickets are being released tomorrow (Friday 26th) at 12pm on the tickets page. More tickets will become available as we get closer to HACKED, so if you&amp;#8217;re not successful keep an eye on the blog and the mailing list for info about future releases.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
